Women Against War; Records apap391
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Yahoo Group Correspondence, 2002-2021
  - OWN Women Against War Action, 2001
    - "Leadbelly" Film to be shown on Saturday, 2/12 at 7:30 PM, FUUSA, Albany, 2011 February 10
    - Event on March 8, Interntational Women's Day, 2011 February 11
    - Stop a bloodbath in Egypt, 2011 February 11
    - Updated Info on reaper drones and Syracuse with links to two articles and lots of important background information, 2011 February 13
    - Tribesman in Pakistan prot drone attacks..., 2011 February 13
    - Documentary: "Billboard from Bethlehem" Feb 16th, 6:30 PM, Pine Hills Lobrary. Mural by Israeli & Palinian Children posted on Connecticut interstate., 2011 February 15
    - Grannies Valentines Event Conveys Strong Message!, 2011 February 15
    - [bethlehem_for_peace] BNP Weekly Peace Email 2/15/2011, 2011 February 15
    - Congress Voting to Kill Public Radio, 2011 February 16
    - Beyond Belief - Special Film Event - Sunday, March 27, 2011, 2011 February 16
    - FW: Alarm Over Proposed Funding Cuts to Foreign Aid, 2011 February 16
    - Free training: Tuesday, February 22nd, all day, at SUNY Albany- The Military & Sexual Violence, 2011 February 17
    - Re: WAWaction Free training: Tuesday, February 22nd, all day, at SUNY Albany- The Military & Sexual Violence, 2011 February 17
    - Stand Up For Women's Health - Rally - Foley Square, NYC - Feb 26th 1:30 to 3:00 PM, local bus from Albany, 2011 February 18
    - Egyptian solidarity with U.S. - A picture is worth a 1000 words!, 2011 February 20
    - A Free Film to Celebrate the 50th Anniversary of the Peace Corps, 2011 February 23
    - Christian Science Monitor: Why Monsanto's GM seeds are undemocratic, 2011 February 23
    - Solidarity with the people of Wisconsin, Saturday, 2/26, 12 Noon, State Capitol, Washington & Swan, Albany, 2011 February 24
    - Join Women On The Bridge - Tuesday, March 8, 2011, 2011 February 24
    - Stand with Wisconsin Workers - Sat. 2/26, Noon, 2011 February 25
    - So. Sudan's leader come to talk at La Moyne College - Syracuse, 2011 February 27
    - : Time to Rally for a Better NY for ALL!! Tuesday March 1st, 12:15 PM - 1 PM, at the W side of the Capitol, 2011 February 28
    - "Army of None" A counter recruitment book, 2011 March 1
    - Vijay Prashad to speak about the Egyptian Revolution, at the Oakwood Community Center, Troy, Friday, March 11, 7pm, 2011 March 1
    - University at Albany, International Women's Day Event, 2011 March 2
    - Assistance needed for newly arrived immigrants Please forward, 2011 March 2
    - Rachel Corrie vigil, 2011 March 2
    - We're back! Spring Season begins at the Sanctuary, 2011 March 3
    - Fwd: URGENT DRONE ACTION ALERT, especially for Senator Schumer, 2011 March 4
    - Fwd: sharing the oil for PEACE (Sudan), 2011 March 4
    - Join" Women On The Bridge" - Tuesday, March 8, 2011, International Women's Day, 4:30--5:30 PM, Albany, 2011 March 5
    - Huwaida Arraf, Israeli Blockade of Gaza and Free Gaza movement, Monday, March 7th, 7 PM Union College, 2011 March 6
    - Land and People: Stories from Israel and the W Bank, Wednesday, March 9, 7:30 PM, Albany, 2011 March 6
    - Just say 'yes' to Guerrilla Mischief, 2011 March 7
    - Our International Women's Day demonstration on Tuesday will be sunny!, 2011 March 7
    - Thanks for taking action! Libya no-fly zone, 2011 March 8
    - : [bethlehem_for_peace] BNP Weekly Peace Email 3/9/2011, 2011 March 9
    - Vaneeta Palecanda reads story on globalization impact on India, 3/24, 6:30 PM, 2011 March 11
    - Troy, Saratoga: Defend the American Dream Against Right Wing Budget Cuts & attacks on Unions, 2011 March 13
    - April 9: Stop the Wars, Stop the War on Muslims, Stop the War on Unions!Please Let Us Know ASAP if you're planning to take the bus to NYC, 2011 March 14
    - Taking 'Women' Seriously at the United Nations-Women's NGOs Made it Happen, March 15th, 7 PM, 2011 March 14
    - Thu 3-17 meeting of United Nations re Egypt reform & WAWaction Taking 'Women' Seriously at the UN, 2011 March 14
    - Reminder: Rachel Corrie vigil, Wednesday, 3/16, 4:30 PM to 5:30 PM, Armory at Washington & Lark, Albany, 2011 March 15
    - Save the Date! April 3, 2 PM, for Children at the Well, interfaith storytelling by youth, In Troy this year., 2011 March 15
    - House Vote to End the Afghanistan War Please call your representative this morning...., 2011 March 17
    - Friend, do you stand with Planned Parenthood? Rally and speak out, Saturday, March 19th, 11 am, Federal building, 2011 March 17
    - Jayme Stone and Patricio Guzman, 2011 March 17
    - March 28 program on drones in Schenectady, 2011 March 17
    - Reminder: Sunday, March 27th, 6:30 to 8:30 PM, FUUSA film showing of "Beyond Belief" and speaker, Susan Retik (9/11 widow and founder of Beyond the 11th.), 2011 March 18
    - Please support Nobel Peace laureate Adolfo Perez Esquivel, 2011 March 18
    - U.S. Boat to Gaza Update #2, 2011 March 18
    - Tonko votes yes to remove US forces from Afghanistan - please thank him! [and a bit more background information.....], 2011 March 18
    - Wed., March 23, Hindu Temple Society, 6:30 tour, 7 PM Wisdom Story circle, Albany at the Hindu Temple, 2011 March 18
    - Wednesday, March 30, 7 PM Forum at Albany Law School on CMUs and solitary confinement in Federal Prisons, 2011 March 19
    - The Nevada Desert Experience Invites you to...., 2011 March 19
    - Useful analysis on Libya: Alternatives to military strikes, 2011 March 21
    - 100 Imams for April 9th - get on the bus, 2011 March 21
    - Blog article about "Beyond Belief" - Muslim Women - Religion, culture and Islam - timesunion.com, 2011 March 25
    - Stop 'Corrective Rape' -- let's reach 1 million, 2011 March 25
    - [unac] April 9 & 10 Antiwar Rallies Will Draw Many Thousands to NYC & San Francisco, 2011 March 25
    - Reminder: Schenectady program on Drones, Monday March 28th 7 PM, preceeded by a short vigil for Japan at 6:45 PM, 2011 March 27
    - HamletIRAN, a version of Hamlet set in Iran during the Green Revolution, Siena College, March 30 through April 10th, details in email:, 2011 March 27
    - Innocent until proven guilty? White House call in Day for Bradley Manning, Monday, March 28, 2011, 9 am to 5 PM, 2011 March 27
    - faith letter against Isamaphobia and for April 9th, 2011 March 27
    - Music, politics, race and revolution, 2011 March 28
    - Fahima Vorgetts coming to Albany again, 2011 March 28
    - Last Chance for Early Bird Special for our Series: "With Love from the Middle East!", 2011 March 28
    - March and Rally: Bring our troops & war dollars home, April 9, 2011 + tax day actions, 2011 March 28
    - Reminder: Wednesday, March 30, 7 PM, at Albany Law School - Event on Solitary Confinement and Isolation in Federal. Prisons, 2011 March 29
    - [bethlehem_for_peace] BNP Weekly Peace Email 3/29/2011, 2011 March 29
    - Bread for World Founder Schenectady Sat April 2, 2011 March 30
    - OTHER-IMPT-APRIL 8th - DISARMaggeddon for peace and climate justice, 2011 March 30
    - Easy way to lobby Tonko & Gibson to defund the new US war - in Libya, 2011 March 31
    - Women as Witnesses to Peace and Justice-Powell House April 15-17. 2011, 2011 April 1
    - [unac] 100 Imams in New York call for support to April 9/10 and more, 2011 April 2
    - Siena College Fair Trade conference program: April 8 (New Dorm), 2011 April 3
    - Panelists at 2 performances of HamletIRAN, 2011 April 4
    - "Civil Liberties in Peril" Wednesday, April 6th at 7 pm Bethlehem Public Library, 2011 April 5
    - This is what resistance looks like!, April 15, Union Square, NYC, 2011 April 5
    - Reskill & resist!, 2011 April 7
    - April 9 & 10 - The response is overwhelming and much more., 2011 April 7
    - Sierra Club "Hydrofracking Rally for Clean Water Not Dirty Drilling" in Albany on 4/11/11, 2011 April 7
    - Stopping the Wars Through the Democrat and Republican Ward, City/Town, and State Committees, 2011 April 8
    - Minerva Speakers Series at Union College, April 11 through May 25 Topic: Oil, The World in Short Supply, 2011 April 10
    - The Global Day of Action on Military Spending Meetup, Albany, NY, Wednesday, April 13th at 11:45 am, Eagle & State Street, 2011 April 10
    - Department of Peace Call - 4/13/11 - Featuring Rep. Dennis Kucinich, 2011 April 11
    - Turn for the worse, 2011 April 11
    - Please vote Bradley Manning the 2011 Time Magazine Man of the Year, 2011 April 11
    - Ground the drones April 16-22 Events and peacewalks from Rocher and Ithaca to Syracuse NY, Rally and Demonstration at Hancock Air Base, April 22nd., 2011 April 12
    - James Howard Kunstler!, 2011 April 12
    - Congress: Keep Your Hands Off Medicare!, 2011 April 13
    - Front page | Satellite Sentinel Project, 2011 April 13
    - Albany women going to Syracuse for the 22nd? Invitation to carpool from Liz Adams in MA, 2011 April 14
    - Urgent: help stop the execution of Troy Davis! And a letter for religious leaders to sign on to as well, 2011 April 14
    - [antiwarUpStateNY] Ground the drones April 16-22, 2011 April 14
    - [bethlehem_for_peace] BNP Weekly Peace Email 4/14/2011, 2011 April 14
    - Refusing to be Enemies: Palinian & Israeli Non-violent Resistance to the Occupation - May 11, 7PM, Siena, 2011 April 15
    - [bethlehem_for_peace] Correction to BNP Weekly Peace Mail (dated 4/14/2011), 2011 April 16
    - Fw: [UNAC-CC] YouTube - Million marchers tell US get out of Iraq by end of 2011 or else, 2011 April 19
    - It's a subMedia weekend!, 2011 April 20
    - Bradley Manning supporters prot song disrupt Obama San Francisco speech, 2011 April 22
    - Re: California State Senate Passes Conflict-Free Bill, 2011 April 23
    - Fwd: Resolution Needed for Sudan's Border Crisis, 2011 April 23
    - Media and video links for Hancock Air Base drones action, 4/22, on SPC webpage, 2011 April 23
    - Tuesday, April 26, 5:30 PM and town hall following in Malta: prot the Republican Theft of Medicare and Attack on the Middle Class at Rep. Gibsons town hall, 2011 April 23
    - Beyond Sept 11 Bike Ride, 2011 April 24
    - Daughters & granddaughters welcome at Grannies for Peace Procession & Vigil, Mother's Day Weekend, 2011 April 25
    - May 2nd: "March on Albany! It's Time to Ban Fracking in New York State!", 2011 April 25
    - Stop government handouts to Big Oil, 2011 April 27
    - [massaction-boston] Fw: Troy Davis' last chance for life, 2011 April 27
    - NY Shoutout! - The Sanctuary, 2011 April 28
    - PRESS RELEASE FarmAssist Productions and Hawthorne Valley:: EXCLUSIVE screening of MILK WAR 5.4.11 @7pm, 2011 April 29
    - Reminder: Peace Procession & Vigil, Mother's Day Weekend, 2011 May 2
    - Thoughts on the Death of Osama Bin Laden from Code Pink, 2011 May 2
    - OTHER Vote Tomorrow: Tell Your Representative to Vote No on Outrageous Abortion Bill, 2011 May 3
    - WAM Theatre/O Solo Mama Mia Fival May 5-8, 2011 May 3
    - "Terror" Sanctuary for Independent Media announcements, 2011 May 5
    - Iraqi Refugee Project program: Know Your Rights Workshop May 7th at Albany Library Main Branch, 2011 May 5
    - Tuesday, May 10th, 9:30 am: All-out to combat Islamophobia and racism in Brooklyn, 2011 May 6
    - Reminder: An Evening with Maxine Kaufman-Lacusta, Wednesday, May 11, 7-9 PM Siena College "Refusing to be Enemies", 2011 May 6
    - BNP Weekly Peace Email 5/4/2011 Some upcoming items for the next week(s) and a requ for donations, 2011 May 8
    - [unac] U.S. Attorney Escalates Attacks, 2011 May 9
    - Beyond Belief Beyond the Bike, 2011 May 10
    - The Sanctuary - Calling our random family home!, 2011 May 11
    - Demand the Release of Dr. Mazin Qumsiyeh and others. Call your government to stop supporting Apartheid regime, 2011 May 16
    - Report on Grannies for Peace wonderful Tulip Fival event, 2011 May 16
    - "Budrus" film May 22 - about nonviolence Palinian efforts and cooperation between Palinian groups and Israelis, 2011 May 16
    - Contact Information from Beth Adams re: Demand the Release of Dr. Mazin Qumsiyeh and others., 2011 May 16
    - Re: WAWaction Report on Grannies for Peace wonderful Tulip Fival event, 2011 May 16
    - 3rd (Good) Update on Dr. Mazin Qumsiyeh, will be released on bail tomorrow, 2011 May 16
    - Guitar benefit concert for Albany's Koinonia Primary Health Care Clinic: Saturday May 21, 7 PM at FUUSA, 405 Washington Avenue, Albany, 2011 May 17
    - More comments about the Report on Grannies for Peace wonderful Tulip Fival event on May 7th., 2011 May 17
    - Iran: Call for release of women's rights activist Maryam Bahreman, detained Wednesday, May 11, 2011, 2011 May 17
    - Reception & Program on National Budget Priorities, Friday, May 20th, Delmar NY, 7 to 9 PM, 2011 May 18
    - ACLU: Oppose New Worldwide War Authority. Plus a link to a news article that explains more, 2011 May 18
    - Honduras Delegation Report Back, 2011 May 18
    - Poster for GN Space Organizing Conference - June 17-19, 2011 May 18
    - Reminder: Budrus, Sunday, 5/22 7 PM at The Linda, 339 Central Avenue, Albany, followed by a panel discussion, 2011 May 19
    - Targeted and Entrapped an excellent report [in PDF form] about the discriminatory targeting of Muslim communities in US counter-terrorism invigations, 2011 May 19
    - Fw: Today National Conference Call - US War Aims and Upswing in Islamophobia, 2011 May 19
    - Film "Battlefront Wisconsin" and Presentation about the assult on Public Health and Safety, Saturday, 5/21, 7:30 PM FUUSA, Albany, 2011 May 19
    - It's Not Just A Game, 6 PM Potluck and 8 PM film with Sportswriter and filmmaker, Dave Zirin, at The Sanctuary, Troy, 2011 May 20
    - Time to Exit Afghanistan Call-in/ E-Mail Day Tuesday, May 24, 2011 May 20
    - Corrected e-mail for Gibson for Exit Afghanistan Call-in/ E-Mail Day Tuesday, May 24, 2011 May 23
    - Urgent Action Alert for Peace in Afghanistan, 2011 May 24
    - In an exciting development, Hundreds of Bahrainis join call to end US support for Bahrain gov't, 2011 May 24
    - Permanent Presidential war powers amendment approved in the House Armed Services Committee on May 11th. Please contact your Representative, 2011 May 25
    - Contact Our Senators for a Real Exit from Afghanistan, 2011 May 25
    - Urge the Obama Administration to protect Libyans, Syrians, and Yemenis in the U.S., 2011 May 30
    - Oil Companies: Keep out of Colombia's Seven Coloured Sea!, 2011 May 31
    - "Gasland" to be shown at the Bethlehem Public Library, Thursday, June 2, 6:30 to 8:45 PM, 2011 May 31
    - Refugee Month 2011: Celebrating Our Refugee Neighbors, 2011 June 1
    - Join us for the finale! Todd Nelson's TN3, Saturday, June 4 at 8 PM, 2011 June 2
    - US Boat to Gaza: WE ARE UNARMED AND WE ARE SAILING, 2011 June 2
    - thank you, 2011 June 2
    - Victory! Gov. Cuomo suspends unjust federal deportation program, 2011 June 2
    - From Egypt to Pakistan: Talk with Global Women this month!, 2011 June 2
    - Useful statement on US and NATO, 2011 June 3
    - Fwd: Sudan Government Attacks, 2011 June 5
    - Day of Action: June 15th, NYC, Newburgh 4 Sentencing, Demand Justice!, 2011 June 6
    - Pressure Building for Withdrawal from Afghanistan, we've contacted our Representatives and now we need to contact Senator Schumer!, 2011 June 7
    - [bethlehem_for_peace] BNP Weekly Peace Email 6/9/2011, 2011 June 9
    - Petition to remove a misleading hydrofracking ad from CNN, 2011 June 11
    - From Albany to Jurez, help us push for peace! FOR action call., 2011 June 12
    - Re: Ride needed to Clearwater Hudson River Revival - Sunday 6/19/2011, 2011 June 12
    - Please spread the word and act: Tomorrow/Tues--- Ground the Drones Call in Day Tuesday June 14th 2011, 2011 June 13
    - Tues. June 14 in Albany: NY farmworkers mobilize, 11 am to 2 PM and legislative visits, 2011 June 13
    - Take this poll on national priorities, sponsored by Peace Action and other Peace groups, 2011 June 13
    - Picnic, Saturday, June 18th,1pm - 5pm, Ballston Spa: The MoveOn NY Capital Region & Saratoga Councils invite you to a Progressive Picnic, 2011 June 14
    - Please thank Schumer for calling for 'sizeable' Afghan troop reduction, 2011 June 15
    - Father's Day Picnic by Turkish Cultural Center Albany, Sunday, 6/19, 1PM to 6 PM, Thacher Park, 2011 June 16
    - Bill McKibben :: 5 days and counting... Tuesday, June 21. 5:30 pm, 2011 June 16
    - Stop Monsanto's anti-organic propaganda on public radio, 2011 June 17
    - Are YOUR Senators Speaking Out Against Unauthorized U.S. War in Libya?, Call or email. Good background articles., 2011 June 17
    - Fw: RESPONSE PLANS and LETTER TO OBAMA if Israel attacks the "Stay Human" Flotilla to Gaza, 2011 June 19
    - October2011.org | "Stop the Machine! Create a New World!", 2011 June 20
    - WELCOME THE PASTORS FOR PEACE FRIENDSHIPMENT 10 CARAVAN, Wednesday, July 6, 5:30 to 8:30 PM, First Presbyterian Church, Albany, 2011 June 20
    - Prot the continued US/NATO war on Libya, 2011 June 21
    - Women Against War co-sponsors the 6/27 Rally Against War in Libya, Monday 6/27 from 12:30 to 1:30 PM, Federal Building, Albany, 2011 June 24
    - Nuclear Abolition Day - Saturday, June 25th. - Action requ., 2011 June 25
    - Reminder - Stop the bombing of Libya prot - Tomorrow (Monday) at noon, 2011 June 26
    - Emergency Response Plan in Case of Israeli Attack on Freedom Flotilla to Gaza, 2011 June 27
    - Stop the Free Trade Act Madness, 2011 June 28
    - Introducing... Freedom Square! First Event, Saturday, July 2nd from 4 PM to 8 PM, 2011 June 28
    - Save the date: Cynthia McKinney to speak in Albany, Sunday, July 10, 3 PM to 5 PM, 2011 June 29
    - Let Hope Sail! Urge State Dept to Support freedom Flotilla to Gaza, 2011 June 30
    - Urgent: Fracking emergency: Please call Gov. Cuomo, 2011 July 1
    - The situation of the US Boat to Gaza and what you can do to help. Please call and email the Greek government., 2011 July 1
    - Our declaration of independents and Debo Band, Saturday July 2nd 4--8 PM, 2011 July 1
    - Fwd: Stand with Aung San Suu Kyi, 2011 July 1
    - Last update for July 1st US Boat to Gaza, 2011 July 2
    - SAVE THE CLEAN AIR ACT, 2011 July 2
    - ACTION ALERT: Tell U.S. government to pressure Greece to release captain and boat!, 2011 July 3
    - The Gaza flotilla: background information and an update (The 8 fasters have been released but the Captain is still in jail), 2011 July 3
    - Native American activist, artist and political prisoner Leonard Peltier in Solitary Confinement, He Needs Your Help!, 2011 July 3
    - Pastors For Peace Caravan - Wednesday, July 6, 5:30 - 8:30 p.m., 2011 July 5
    - Cynthia McKinney - Sunday, July 10, 3:00 - 5:00 p.m., 2011 July 7
    - TODAY-Call Gov. Rick Parry- Stop Leal's Execution, 2011 July 7
    - Reminder Cynthia McKinney just back from Libya today at 3 pm, 2011 July 10
    - Our Tea Party- attend one of 1,500 American Dream meetings next week - near YOU!, 2011 July 11
    - Save the date: Debut showing of Women in Black film, 2011 July 11
    - [codepinknewyork] Please call DOS for The Audacity of Hope!, 2011 July 12
    - Progressive Communications Job Opening at RESIST! For anyone who might be intered and qualified...., 2011 July 12
    - Arts Against Repression, Friday August 5, 5:30 through 10 PM, Albany. Commemoration, march, music, poetry and food, 2011 July 13
    - 10 years today, a bold call for peace, 2011 July 13
    - Healthcare is a Human Right: The Vermont Experience. Thursday, July 21st 7:00 PM, Albany, NY, 2011 July 13
    - Seeking help and support with a Blood Drive to commemorate September 11th as part of "Muslims for Life", 2011 July 14
    - News update and action requ: Help Free US Boat to Gaza from Greek Military Dock!, 2011 July 14
    - "Making Music for Peace", Thursday, July 21, 7 PM to 8:30 PM, Bethlehem Town Hall, 2011 July 16
    - Arts Against Repression, August 5, 5:30PM, Albany - Everyone Welcome!, 2011 July 16
    - Flotilla II still sailing: French boat Dignite of Freedom Flotilla II leaves Greece for Gaza [+ Passenger List], 2011 July 17
    - Reminder: Healthcare is a Human Right: Lessons from Vermont. Thursday, July 21st, 7:00 pm. Albany, 2011 July 18
    - Pls come - Gaza Flotilla Emergency Demonstration: July 20, 5-6PM, Central Ave & Wolf Rd, 2011 July 19
    - Requ regarding US hikers held in Iran: July 25 through July 28, a call in week to the Iranian Inters Section in Washington DC, and an Organizational Sign on letter...Read on------->, 2011 July 20
    - Tell the Pentagon to stop retaliation against whistle blower who saved thousands of lives, 2011 July 20
    - Saratoga, Kinderhook & around the state: "Rore the American Promise - Caravan July 20-21", 2011 July 20
    - Fw: A National Park to glorify the Atomic Bomb?, 2011 July 21
    - [NEW PRIORITIES] ALERT: Don't cut Social Security! Cut the Pentagon!, 2011 July 23
    - Action Call: Tell Washington: Don't Veto Palinian Independence!, 2011 July 24
    - [massaction-boston] Jailed Palinian leader asks millions to prot - Solidarity demo planned at UN 9-15-11, 2011 July 24
    - Tuesday[7/26]: Emergency drop by at Representative Chris Gibson's office - Don't DEFAULT, 2011 July 25
    - [bethlehem_for_peace] BNP Weekly Peace Email 7/25/2011, 2011 July 25
    - REMINDER: Please call the Iranian Inters Section [July 25 through July 29th] and ask them to Free US hikers held in Iran, 2011 July 26
    - Please take a few minutes today to support Bradley Manning, National Call in Day to White House and Secretary of the Army, 2011 July 27
    - FW: Billionaires Behaving Badly, 2011 July 27
    - "We are Still Standing" at the Madison Theater, Wednesday, August 10, 7 PM and 9 PM, 2011 July 28
    - Next Affinity Group Meeting for Oct 6 this Sat July 30, at 1 PM in front of the Saratoga Post Office, 2011 July 28
    - Hiroshima-Nagasaki Calendar of Events Wednesday, August 3, 2011 through Tuesday, August 9, 2011, 2011 July 29
    - WAWaction Hiroshima-Nagasaki Calendar of Events Change in the Troy Event on August 6th, no film showing, 2011 July 30
    - Awakening to the "Circle of Life", 13th Annual Kateri Tekakwitha Peace Conference-Friday evening and Saturday, 8/19 and 8/20, 2011 July 31
    - Please thank Representative Paul Tonko for signing the Lee-Jones letter, calling for withdrawal of US troops from Iraq by 12/11, 2011 July 31
    - Friday, August 5, 12:00pm - 1:00pm - Vigil for Jobs, 2011 August 2
    - Hiroshima/Nagasaki Commemoration Events, 2011 August 2
    - Reminder: ARTS AGAINST REPRESSION - FRIDAY AUG 5 - ALL WELCOME, 2011 August 3
    - A Volunteer Opportunity to mentor refugee families, and two dates for US Committee for Refugees & Immigrants orientations, 2011 August 4
    - Paul Tonko Town Meeting - Please go with a peace message!, 2011 August 4
    - Commemoration of Tom Little at Afghan exhibit reception tonight from 5 PM to 8 PM, Albany, 2011 August 5
    - "It's an Uptown Summer!" & details of the Peace Pilgrimage programs starting at 2 PM, Saturday, August 6th. Potluck from 6-7 PM, 2011 August 5
    - Reminder: "We Are Still Standing Stories of Women In Black", Madison Avenue Theatre, Wednesday, 8/10, 7 PM and 9 PM, 2011 August 7
    - Rebuild the Dream "Where Are The Jobs?" Rally Wednesday, August 10th from 11 am to 1 PM, Capital Park W, Albany, 2011 August 8
    - Call For Singers: HOLLY NEAR CONCERT, Orientation and open rehearsal, SYRACUSE, Wednesday, September 21, 2011, 6:15 PM, 2011 August 9
    - Randy Kehler and Eric Marczak.... Friday, August 19th and Saturday, August 20, 2011, 2011 August 9
    - Please help get this project off the ground. Documentary about Palinian Nonviolent Resistance, 2011 August 11